DOMINIK AMRUGIEWICZ

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER





ABOUT

Front End Web Developer with 5+ years of experience in developing and implementing frontend applications. Specialized in working with React and API's. Whether it's business or private stoked about developing, clean coding and always reliable at work.

EXPERIENCE

2019 - PRESENT

WEB DEVELOPER

SIRUP GmbH · Berlin, Germany

- Building a video learn platform for <u>Engelhard</u> with React and React Native. Application conncted via REST to a backend. React Native application published in <u>Apple App Store</u> and <u>Android Play Store</u>
- Building NextJS Website connected to headless Drupal system for <u>Penguin Random</u> <u>House</u>
- Frontend implementation for <u>Science Olympiaden</u> based on Zeplin design with the Twig template enginge, SASS and JavaScript ES6 Modules
- \cdot Magento 2 Shop frontend implementation for <u>Meyer Hosen</u>
- Revise React Application for $\underline{\mathsf{Meyer}\;\mathsf{Hosen}}$ B2B Shop
- · Creating HTML Newsletter Templates
- · Ticket support for customers

2015 - PRESENT

FREELANCER WEB DEVELOPMENT

Berlin, Germany

- Setting up Wordpress websites for Photograph <u>Julian Melzer</u>, Artist <u>Kerstin Kohlmann</u> <u>and Hair & Make Up Artist Teresa Hofmeister</u>
- · Club website made with Gatsby and headless Wordpress for <u>TuS 1984 Neuhausen</u>
- · Creating websites with HTML / CSS / JavaScript

2015

WORKING STUDENT

Loyaltyplant Germany Gmb · Berlin, Germany

- · Design webiste templates in Photoshop for schalt up
- · Creating marketing materials for Happywall

EDUCATION

2021

${\tt NANODEGREE} \cdot {\tt FULL} \; {\tt STACK} \; {\tt JAVASCRIPT} \; {\tt DEVELOPER}$

Udacity

- · Developing with TypeScript
- · Backend Development with Node.js
- · Creating an API with PostgreSQL and Express
- · Angular Fundamentals
- · Deployment Processes

2016 - 2019

TRAINING IT SPECIALIST

SIRUP GmbH · Berlin, Germany

- · Converting designs from Sketch to frontend applications
- Working with different CMS like drupal and magento
- · Ticket support for customers

2013 - 2016

BACHELOR OF APPLIED COMPUTER SCIENCE

HTW Berlin \cdot Berlin, Germany \cdot 2015 - 2016 HS Worms \cdot Worms, Germany \cdot 2013 - 2015

- · Software Engineering and Development
- · Visual Computing
- · Networks and Security

SKILLS

React / React Native	professional	API / REST	advanced
JavaScript / ES6	professional	Magento	advanced
HTML / CSS / SASS	professional	TypeScript	good
Bootstrap	excellent	Supabase / AWS	good
Taildwind CSS	advanced	Node.js / Express	good
Git / GitHub / GitLab	advanced	Webpack / NPM / Yarn	good

CERTIFICATES

2021

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER NANODEGREE

2019 TRAINING IT SPECIALIST